JACK BURNETT

PROFILE

I am a PhD student in the Interactive AI CDT at the University of Bristol, with prior lecturing experience in FE and HE provisions. Within my research, I am currently exploring how human-in-the-loop AI systems can be utilised in educational settings. My research builds upon the skills I developed throughout my MSc, BSc, and PGCE teachings. As a BSc Computer Science Graduate, I have studied the fundamental theories of Computer Programming, Computer Architecture, Artificial Intelligence, and Mathematics; these have been furthered through my PhD studies.

EDUCATION

INTERACTIVE AI PHD | UNIVERSITY OF BRISOL | SEPTEMBER 2023 - PRESENT

Working Research Title: Creating an accessible physical interface development toolkit with generative AI and parametric design

Taught Modules: Machine Learning Paradigms, Dialogue and Narrative, Uncertainty Modelling for Intelligent Systems, Computational Logic for AI, Research Methods for Interactive AI.

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY MSC | UWE BRISOL | SEPTEMBER 2021 - AUGUST 2023

Graduated with Distinction

Key Modules: Project Management, Digital Design and Development, Designing the User Experience, Machine Learning, Strategy and Governance in IT, and Information Security.

Dissertation Topic: 'The Opportunities and Risks of AI in Mental Health Diagnosis'

PGCE SECONDARY COMPUTER SCIENCE | UWE BRISOL | SEPTEMBER 2020 - JULY 2021

Graduated with Pass and QTS

Key Modules: Pedagogical Approaches, Educational Policy, and Evidence-based Practice.

COMPUTER SCIENCE BSC (HONS) | UNIVERSITY OF BATH | OCTOBER 2017 – JULY 2020

Graduated with Honorary Second-Class Upper Division (2:1)

Key Modules: Principles of Programming, Computer Systems Architecture, Discrete Mathematics, Human-Computer Interaction, Fundamentals of Visual Computing, Functional Programming, Artificial Intelligence, Entrepreneurship, Intelligent Agents, Networking, and Safety-Critical Systems.

Dissertation Topic: 'Developing an Open-Source Research Application to Monitor and Analyse Phone Usage and its Effects on Users, alongside Potential Personal Informatics Tools'

SKILLS & ABILITIES

Excellent Organizational Skills, Timekeeping, Logical Thinking, Teamwork, Independent Learning, Resilience and Resourcefulness. Programming: C, C#, Java, Python, MATLAB, SQL, Haskell and PHP.

EXPERIENCE

LECTURER | WESTON COLLEGE, WESTON-SUPER-MARE | AUGUST 2021-JANUARY 2024

Role responsibilities: Lecturing on Data Analysis (Level 4) and Data Analytics (Level 6) on BSc Digital and Technological Solutions, lecturing on Digital T-Levels and Level 3 BTEC Applied Computing with a focus on Data and Programming. Development of a Digital UX degree apprenticeship.

STUDENT TEACHER | CALDICOT SCHOOL, CALDICOT, WALES | APRIL 2021-JUNE 2021

Role responsibilities: Teaching Years 7, 8, 9, 10, and 12 Computer Science and IT; Teaching Year 12 Business. Using formative assessment and summative assessment for end-of-year grading.

STUDENT TEACHER | KINGSMEAD SCHOOL, TAUNTON | NOVEMBER 2020-APRIL 2021

Role responsibilities: Preparing and teaching remote and in-class learning for Years 7, 8, 9, and 10. Extra-curricular 'Wii Wednesdays' during lunchtimes. Assisting with a set tutor group.

VOLUNTEERING

EDUCATIONAL SPEAKER | CATS PROTECTION | SEPTMEBER 2023-PRESENT

Role responsibilities: Ambassador for Cats Protection, raising awareness of the charity, enhancing children's understanding of feline welfare, and providing information sessions for local groups.

QUALIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

Enhanced DBS check (with update service)

Awarded by: DBS/Gov.uk

Full driving license

Awarded by: DVLAW

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

Programming & Software engineering, Video Gaming, Contemporary Technology, Researching, Puzzle games, Managing Online Communities, Al research, Arduino, Card Games, Animals.

PROFESSIONAL BODY MEMBERSHIPS

British Computer Society - Professional membership
Institute of Engineering and Technology - Professional membership

REFERENCES

Previous Academic References available on request